sopantech.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy

**www.sopantech.com** will notify you when it is collecting personally identifiable information about you, as well as the use or uses sopantech.com intends to make with such information. For example, we may need to collect information to respond to your requests for information, in connection with content entry forms and/or promotions, or to allow you to send or post messages.

## IP Addresses

Gone are the days of building simple websites. Clients are demanding more functionality and better results from their websites and we create unforgettable brand experiences. Our passion is helping design and build solutions that strike the perfect balance between users, business, and technology. 

## Use of Cookies

When you view our web site, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a 'Cookie' or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a web site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. 

## Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information about our visitors is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted by those visitors. sopantech.com uses such information only for the purpose for which it was is submitted, unless we disclose other uses at the time of collection. sopantech.com does not sell personal information to third parties. sopantech.com may share personally identifiable information with other parts of our company, but this will never be used on an individual basis outside of the company. sopantech.com maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of personally identifiable information in its possession. sopantech.com may use such personally identifiable information in the aggregate (non-identifiable) form to make our web site better and more responsive to the needs of our visitors. This statistical compilation of non-identifiable information may also be used by or provided to others for marketing, advertising, or research purposes. 

## Links to Other Sites

sopantech.com chooses its advertisers and business partners carefully. However, sopantech.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our web sites. These links are meant for the visitor's convenience only. Links to third party web sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by sopantech.com of content, policies or practices of such sites. Once you have left a sopantech.com web site via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. sopantech.com's web site may also be linked to web sites operated by companies affiliated with sopantech.com. Visitors to those sites should refer to their separate privacy policies and practices. 

## Comments and Submissions

Should any visitor to sopantech.com.'s web site provide information, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas or any material through the feedback mechanisms located in the web site, sopantech.com shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such information and shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute the information to others without limitation. The information expressed in any Message Boards, or other forums conducted on sopantech.com's web sites ("Forums") are not necessarily those of sopantech.com or its affiliated or related entities or content providers and sopantech.com makes no representations or warranties regarding that information or those opinions.
